Guide to the James Lees-Milne Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- Correspondence, 1923-97; Series I; 7.35; (18 boxes)
  - FAMILY CORRESPONDENCE
    - Other family correspondence, 1930-96 (Box 17, Folder 853)
  - UNIDENTIFIED
    - Lees-Milne, James, 1933-90, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 854)
      Drafts and copies of outgoing
      letters, recipients unidentified
    - "Aart", 1990-95 (Box 18, Folder 855)
    - "Brigid", 1995 (Box 18, Folder 856)
    - "Cotters", 1991, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 857)
    - "Dick", 1992-97 (Box 18, Folder 858)
    - "Doreen", n.d. (Box 18, Folder 859)
    - "Emma" and "John", 1985-97 (Box 18, Folder 860)
    - "Gilbert", 1985-90 (Box 18, Folder 861)
    - "Heck", 1996-97 (Box 18, Folder 862)
    - "Isabel", 1990-94 (Box 18, Folder 863)
    - "Linda", 1996, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 864)
    - "Pat", 1990-96 (Box 18, Folder 865)
    - "Sarah", 1973-97 (Box 18, Folder 866)
    - General first names A-J, 1933-97 (Box 18, Folder 867)
    - General first names L-V, 1939-97 (Box 18, Folder 868)
    - Illegible and unsigned, 1940-96 (Box 18, Folder 869)
- Writings, 1907-94; Series II; 2.94; (7 boxes)
  Series II, Writings, is organized into two subseries, Diaries and Other Writings. Diaries is arranged chronologically. Other Writings is arranged alphabetically by title, with the exception of shorter works, which are grouped together under a separate heading at the end of the alphabetical sequence.
  - DIARIES
    - Ancestral Voices [1942-1943]
      - Contract and notes, 1974, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 870)
      - Reviews, 1975-76 (Box 19, Folder 871)
        Includes letter from JL-M to Times Literary Supplement
    - Prophesying Peace [1944-1945]
      - Contract, 1976 (Box 19, Folder 872)
      - Preface, typescript, corrected, 1977 (Box 19, Folder 873)
      - Reviews, 1977-95 (Box 19, Folder 874)
        Includes letter from JL-M to The Times
    - Caves of Ice [1946-1947]
      - Contract, 1982 Apr 15 (Box 19, Folder 875)
      - Original diary fragment, holograph, 1947 (Box 19, Folder 876)
        Inscribed to John Byrne:
        "2 pages of unedited and
        undestroyed MS of diary.
        JL-M 1-8-97"
      - Typescript carbon, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 877-878)
      - Index, holograph (Box 19, Folder 879)
      - Reviews, 1983-84 (Box 19, Folder 880)
    - Midway on the Waves [1948-1949]
      - Contract, 1985 Feb 15 (Box 19, Folder 881)
      - Notes and Foreword, holograph and typescript carbon, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 882)
      - Reviews, 1985-87 (Box 19, Folder 883)
    - Diary [1953-1978]
      Published in edited form as A Mingled Measure [1953-72], Ancient as the Hills [1973-74], and Through Wood and Dale [1975-78]
      - Original diary pages, holograph and typescript, corrected, 1953-78 (Box 19, Folder 884-886)
  - OTHER WRITINGS
    - The Age of Adam
      - Reviews, 1948-51 (Box 19, Folder 887)
    - The Age of Inigo Jones
      - Research correspondence, background material, and notes, 1951-52 (Box 19, Folder 888)
        Includes one of JL-M's "Red
        Books," pocket notebooks kept
        during National Trust property
        visits; correspondence from
        Gaetano Cozzi
      - Reviews, 1953-54 (Box 19, Folder 889)
    - Another Self
      - Contracts, 1969-70 (Box 20, Folder 890)
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 891-892)
      - Notes, [1969] (Box 20, Folder 893)
      - Reviews, 1970-84 (Box 20, Folder 894)
    - Aristocracy (work in progress)
      - Notes and background material, [1967-69] (Box 20, Folder 895)
    - The Bachelor Duke: The Sixth Duke of Devonshire
      - Reviews, 1991 (Box 20, Folder 896)
    - Bankes, William John (projected biography)
      - Research correspondence and background material, 1982-86 (Box 20, Folder 897)
        Includes photograph of portrait
    - Baroque Europe
      Review
    - Baroque in Italy
      - Reviews, 1959-60 (Box 20, Folder 898)
    - The Country House
      - Contract and notes, 1981 (Box 20, Folder 899)
      - Reviews, 1982-83 (Box 20, Folder 900)
    - Earls of Creation
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 901-902)
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 903)
      - Reviews, 1962-63 (Box 20, Folder 904)
    - English Country Houses: Baroque, 1685-1715
      - Notes and bibliography (Box 21, Folder 905)
      - Research correspondence and background material, 1967, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 906)
        Includes letters from
        Geoffrey W. Beard
      - Reviews, 1970-71 (Box 21, Folder 907)
    - The Enigmatic Edwardian
      - Contract, 1983 May 16 (Box 21, Folder 908)
      - Background material, 1907, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 909)
        Includes a letter from Esher
        to "Joe," 1907 Nov 12; and
        photographs
      - Research correspondence and notes, 1982-86 (Box 21, Folder 910)
        Includes letters from Anita
        Shane Leslie, Owen Lloyd-George,
        James Handyside Marshall-Cornwall,
        the Duke of Portland, Kenneth Rose,
        Oliver Everett, Robert Rhodes James
      - Reviews, 1986-89 (Box 21, Folder 911)
    - Harold Nicolson: a Biography
      Volume I
      - Contract, 1979 Oct 15 (Box 21, Folder 912)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 913-919)
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 920)
      - Draft, typescript fragments, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 921)
      - Extract printed in Saturday Review, 1980 Oct 25 (Box 22, Folder 922)
      - Research correspondence and notes, 1977-80 (Box 22, Folder 923)
        John Gore
      - Background material and notes (Box 22, Folder 924)
      - Reviews, 1980-88 (Box 22, Folder 925)
      - Volume II
        - Contract, 1981 Mar 11 (Box 22, Folder 926)
        - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 927-932)
        - Notes, n.d. (Box 22, Folder 933)
        - Reviews, 1981-85 (Box 22, Folder 934)
      - Background material
        - Obituary by JL-M, typescript and version printed in The Sunday Telegraph, 1968 May 5 (Box 23, Folder 935)
        - Dictionary of National Biography entry by JL-M, draft, typescript, [1976] (Box 23, Folder 936)
        - Obituaries and appreciations of HN and Vita Sackville-West by other writers, 1962-68 (Box 23, Folder 937)
        - List of correspondents kept by Elvira Niggeman, 1938-64 (Box 23, Folder 938)
        - List of HN's reviews in The Observer, [1946-61] (Box 23, Folder 939)
        - 70th birthday subscription, 1956 (Box 23, Folder 940)
          Includes letters to John Sparrow
          from contributors, list of
          contributors, formal letter to
          HN, and notes
        - Photographs of and poems about HN (Box 23, Folder 941)
      - Correspondence of Harold Nicolson
        - Bagnold, Enid (Lady Jones), letters to [Photocopies], 1931-63 (Box 23, Folder 942)
        - Beaverbrook, Max Aitken, Baron, letters to and from, 1929-31 (Box 23, Folder 943)
        - Evening Standard, letter from editor G. Gilliat, 1929 Sep 13 (Box 23, Folder 944)
        - Lockhart, Robert Hamilton Bruce, Sir, letters to and from, 1929 (Box 23, Folder 945)
        - Margerie, Roland de, letters to and from [Photocopies and one original from RdM], 1929-1953, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 946)
        - Niggeman, Elvira, letters to, 1938-63 (Box 23, Folder 947-948)
          With two letters from Vita
          Sackville-West, one from
          Rupert Hart-Davis, and one from
          Doubleday & Co.; many are
          annotated by Miss Niggeman
        - Pope-Hennessy, James, letters to [Photocopies], 1937-63 (Box 23, Folder 949)
          With one letter from Elvira
          Niggeman, and one from HN to
          Dame Una Pope-Hennessy
        - Preston, Stuart, letters to, 1938-56 (Box 23, Folder 950)
        - Sackville-West, Vita, telegrams from, letter to [Photocopy], 1929-36 (Box 23, Folder 951)
        - Woolf, Leonard; Woolf, Virginia, letters from, 1929 Jul 24 (Box 23, Folder 952)
        - Other letters to and from HN, 1925-63 (Box 23, Folder 953)
    - Heretics in Love
      - Contract, 1972 Apr 24 (Box 23, Folder 954)
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 955-956)
      - Draft fragments, typescript, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 957)
      - Cover art proof, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 958)
      - Reviews, 1972-73 (Box 23, Folder 959)
    - Images of Bath
      - Draft, typescript, corrected, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 960)
      - Reviews, 1982-5 (Box 24, Folder 961)
    - The Last Stuarts
      - Contract and typescript carbon of outline, 1970 Nov 30, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 962)
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 963-964)
      - Notes and background material, 1970-81, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 965)
      - Research correspondence, 1971-82 (Box 24, Folder 966)
        Brinsley Ford, Oliver Everett
      - Reviews, 1983-84 (Box 24, Folder 967)
    - My Hanoverian Ancestors [by Edward, Duke of Windsor]
      - Notes and background, preparation for edition edited by JL-M (Box 24, Folder 968)
    - National Trust Guide
      - Reviews, 1948 (Box 24, Folder 969)
        See also: Scrapbook, Box 25, folder 986
    - Roman Mornings
      - Reviews, 1956-57 (Box 24, Folder 970)
    - Round the Clock
      - Contract, 1977 Mar 24 (Box 24, Folder 971)
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 972)
    - St. Peter's
      - Contract, 1966 Feb 11 (Box 24, Folder 973)
      - Draft, holograph, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 974-975)
      - Notes, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 976)
      - Background material, 1963, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 977)
      - Reviews, 1967-68 (Box 25, Folder 978)
    - Tudor Renaissance
      - Reviews, 1951-52 (Box 25, Folder 979)
    - Venetian Evenings
      - Reviews, 1991 (Box 25, Folder 980)
    - William Beckford
      - Contract, notes, and background materials, 1975, n.d. (Box 25, Folder 981)
        With photographic reproductions
        of artwork and photograph of tower
      - Notes and bibliography (Box 25, Folder 982)
      - Reviews, 1976-91 (Box 25, Folder 983)
    - Worcestershire: a Shell Guide
      - Reviews, 1964-65 (Box 25, Folder 984)
    - Shorter Writings
      - Magazine and newspaper articles, printed versions and drafts, typescript, 1962-96 (Box 25, Folder 985)
      - Articles published in The Architectural Review, 1937-45
      - Scrapbook: clippings of book reviews and articles by JL-M and others, 1939-67 (Box 25, Folder 986)
      - Loose clippings removed from between pages of scrapbook, 1962-64 (Box 25, Folder 987)
      - "Who Cares for England" BBC radio broadcast, typescript and as later printed in The Listener, 1964 (Box 25, Folder 988)
        With clippings of reviews and
        letters in various newspapers
        following the broadcast
      - Other radio and television scripts (Box 25, Folder 989)
      - Letters to the Editor, printed and holograph, 1955-90 (Box 25, Folder 990)
        See also: Series I, Correspondence, The Times, Box 16, folder 759
      - Memorials and obituaries, typescript, holograph, and printed, 1937-94 (Box 25, Folder 991)
        See also: Harold Nicolson, Box 23, folders 935-936
- Other Papers, 1934-97; Series III; 0.42; (1 box)
  Series III, Other Papers, is arranged alphabetically by type of material.
  - Certificates, 1939-1994 (Box 26, Folder 992)
  - Clippings: articles about JL-M, 1934-95 (Box 26, Folder 993)
  - Clippings: obituaries, 1935-91 (Box 26, Folder 994-996)
    See also: Series II, Writings, Obituaries by JL-M, Box 25, folder 991
    See also: Series II, Writings, Harold Nicolson, Box 23, folders 935-937
  - Clippings: National Trust, [1934]-95 (Box 26, Folder 997)
  - Clippings: various subjects, [1934]-96 (Box 26, Folder 998)
  - Invitations and programs, [1920s]-1997 (Box 26, Folder 999-1000)
  - List of books read, 1962-96 (Box 26, Folder 1001)
  - Miscellaneous papers, 1955-93, n.d. (Box 26, Folder 1002)
    Includes Sandys and Washington
    family tree and Lees-Milne
    Crompton Hall bookplate with
    coat of arms
- Photographs, 1911-1985; Series IV; 0.21; (1 box)
  Series IV, Photographs, is organized
  into three subseries, Family, Friends,
  and Other Subjects. Each is organized
  alphabetically by principal subject.
  Photos of JL-M can be found throughout
  the series, as indicated in the notes
  for individual folders.
  - FAMILY
    - Lees-Milne, Alvilde, 1948-[80s] (Box 27, Folder 1003)
      Includes JL-M, Rosemary Lyttleton,
      Clarissa Luke, and Greg Gowrie
    - Lees-Milne, George Crompton, 1925-[ca. 1950] (Box 27, Folder 1004)
      Includes Harry Horsefield
    - Lees-Milne, Helen, [ca. 1914-40s] (Box 27, Folder 1005)
      Includes JL-M, Richard Stewart-
      Jones, and "DC"
    - Lees-Milne, James, 1920-59 (Box 27, Folder 1006)
      Portraits and individual snapshots
      also includes a 1939 group photo of
      the Red Cross unit in which JL-M
      served, and a photo of Sally
      Churchill in JL-M's arms at her
      christening
      See also: other folders throughout this series
    - Lees-Milne immediate family, 1911-14 (Box 27, Folder 1007)
      Includes JL-M, George Crompton
      Lees-Milne, Helen Lees-Milne,
      Audrey Lees-Milne, and Dick
      (Richard Crompton) Lees-Milne
    - Extended family, 1930-[ca. 1950s] (Box 27, Folder 1008)
      Includes A. Milne Lees-Milne,
      and [Simon Lees-Milne?]
  - FRIENDS
    Bloch, Michael
    See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 2, folder 71
    - Churchill, John Spencer, [ca. 1930s] (Box 27, Folder 1009)
      Includes Anne Gathorne-Hardy,
      Ruth [Gathorne-Hardy?], Kay Halle,
      Betsy Roosevelt, and 2 others
      unidentified
    - Hamilton, Ian, Sir; Hamilton, Jean, Lady
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 6, folder 326
    - Kennet, Kathleen, in [Switzerland?], 1935 (Box 27, Folder 1010)
      Includes JL-M, Wayland Hilton
      Young, Daphne Humphreys, Lady
      Humphreys, and two unidentified
      men
    - Kent, Prince Michael of, and family
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 8, folder 423
    - Kenworthy-Browne, John, 1959, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1011)
    - Kinross/Balfour family, in Argyll, 1934 (Box 27, Folder 1012)
      Includes JL-M, Patrick Kinross,
      Rosemary Balfour, Ursula Balfour,
      Lady Kinross, Frederick Etchells,
      Margaret Sheridan, George Lennox-
      Boyd, and unidentified woman
    - Lloyd, David and Blanche (Lady Lloyd), at Lerici and Clouds Hill, 1931-36 (Box 27, Folder 1013)
      Includes JL-M
    - Long Crichel, [1940s, 1960s] (Box 27, Folder 1014)
      Includes Eardley Knollys, Frank
      Coombs, Raymond Mortimer, Desmond
      Shaw-Taylor, Edward Sackville-West,
      and three others unidentified
    - Mitford family, 1926-27 (Box 27, Folder 1015)
      Includes JL-M, Diana, Nancy, Pamela,
      and Tom Mitford, Randolph and Diana
      Spencer Churchill, and Ralph Jarvis
    - Nicolson, Harold
      See: Series II, Writings, Harold Nicolson, Box 23, folder 941
    - Pope-Hennessy, James, [ca. 1940] (Box 27, Folder 1016)
    - Pope-Hennessy, John, Sir
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Box 13, folder 609
    - Preston, Stuart
      See: Group photos of other friends, Box 27, folder 1020
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Stuart Preston, Box 13, folder 615
    - Sackville-West, Edward, 1942 (Box 27, Folder 1017)
      See also: Long Crichel, Box 27, folder 1014
    - Stewart-Jones, Richard, 1938-[50s] (Box 27, Folder 1018)
      See also: Helen Lees-Milne, Box 27, folder 1005
    - Reid, Victoria
      See: Series I, Correspondence, Victoria Reid, Box 13, folder 634
    - Tewksbury, [ca. 1940s] (Box 27, Folder 1019)
      Includes JL-M, Canon Gough,
      Theodosia Cropper, and
      unidentified woman
    - Group photographs of other friends, [ca. 1930]-85 (Box 27, Folder 1020)
      Includes JL-M, Alfred and
      Clementine Beit, Harry
      d'Avigdor Goldsmid, Mary
      Herbert, Michael Huxley,
      Lady Constance Milnes-Gaskell,
      Mary Milnes-Gaskell, Stuart
      Preston, John Sparrow, and
      unidentified man
  - OTHER SUBJECTS
    Esher, Reginald Balliol Brett,
    2nd Viscount
    - Historical subjects, n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1021)
      Photograph of John Keats's grave
      and photographs of four 18th
      century oil portraits of Robert
      and James Thompson of Camphill
    - "National Trust Meeting April 15, 1912", n.d. (Box 27, Folder 1022)
      Photo of 1912 drawing, with
      copy of identification key
- Oversize, 1.67; (1 box)
  - Letter from John Betjeman (in Series I) (Box 28, Folder 1023)
  - Letter from Eardley Knollys (in Series I) (Box 28, Folder 1024)
  - Midway on the Waves, reviews (in Series II), 1987-96 (Box 28, Folder 1025)
  - Baroque Europe, review (in Series II), 1962 Dec 15 (Box 28, Folder 1026)
  - The Enigmatic Edwardian, reviews (in Series II), 1988 (Box 28, Folder 1027)
  - Harold Nicolson: a Biography, Vol. I., background material (in Series II), 1940-41 (Box 28, Folder 1028)
  - Worcestershire: a Shell Guide, reviews (in Series II), 1965 (Box 28, Folder 1029)
  - Articles by JL-M in The Architectural Review (in Series II), 1937-45 (Box 28, Folder 1030)
  - "Who Cares for England," reviews (in Series II), 1964 (Box 28, Folder 1031)
  - Articles about JL-M (in Series III), 1988-91 (Box 28, Folder 1032)
  - Clippings: obituaries (in Series III), 1978 (Box 28, Folder 1033)
  - Clippings: National Trust (in Series III), 1987 (Box 28, Folder 1034)
  - Clippings: various subjects (in Series III), 1991 (Box 28, Folder 1035)
- Restricted Fragile, 0.42; (1 box)
  Conditions Governing Access
  Restricted fragile material. Reference surrogates have been substituted in the main files. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 3, folder 129 (Box 29, Folder 1036)
  - Box 3, folder 159 (Box 29, Folder 1037)
  - Box 3, folder 186 (Box 29, Folder 1038)
  - Box 6, folder 283 (Box 29, Folder 1039)
  - Box 6, folder 331 (Box 29, Folder 1040)
  - Box 8, folder 394 (Box 29, Folder 1041)
  - Box 10, folder 473 (Box 29, Folder 1042)
  - Box 12, folder 561 (Box 29, Folder 1043)
  - Box 12, folder 567 (Box 29, Folder 1044)
  - Box 13, folder 612 (Box 29, Folder 1044a)
  - Box 14, folder 681 (Box 29, Folder 1045)
  - Box 15, folder 684 (Box 29, Folder 1046)
  - Box 15, folder 701 (Box 29, Folder 1047)
  - Box 16, folder 759 (Box 29, Folder 1048)
  - Box 18, folder 867 (Box 29, Folder 1049)
  - Box 19, folder 871 (Box 29, Folder 1050)
  - Box 19, folder 874 (Box 29, Folder 1051)
  - Box 19, folder 880 (Box 29, Folder 1052)
  - Box 19, folder 883 (Box 29, Folder 1053)
  - Box 19, folder 887 (Box 29, Folder 1054)
  - Box 19, folder 889 (Box 29, Folder 1055)
  - Box 20, folder 894 (Box 29, Folder 1056)
  - Box 20, folder 898 (Box 29, Folder 1057)
  - Box 20, folder 900 (Box 29, Folder 1058)
  - Box 20, folder 904 (Box 29, Folder 1059)
  - Box 21, folder 907 (Box 29, Folder 1060)
  - Box 21, folder 909 (Box 29, Folder 1061)
  - Box 21, folder 911 (Box 29, Folder 1062)
  - Box 22, folder 925 (Box 29, Folder 1063)
  - Box 22, folder 934 (Box 29, Folder 1064)
  - Box 23, folder 935 (Box 29, Folder 1065)
  - Box 23, folder 937 (Box 29, Folder 1066)
  - Box 23, folder 943 (Box 29, Folder 1067)
  - Box 23, folder 951 (Box 29, Folder 1068)
  - Box 23, folder 959 (Box 29, Folder 1069)
  - Box 24, folder 961 (Box 29, Folder 1070)
  - Box 24, folder 965 (Box 29, Folder 1071)
  - Box 24, folder 966 (Box 29, Folder 1072)
  - Box 24, folder 967 (Box 29, Folder 1073)
  - Box 24, folder 969 (Box 29, Folder 1074)
  - Box 24, folder 970 (Box 29, Folder 1075)
  - Box 25, folder 977 (Box 29, Folder 1076)
  - Box 25, folder 978 (Box 29, Folder 1077)
  - Box 25, folder 979 (Box 29, Folder 1078)
  - Box 25, folder 980 (Box 29, Folder 1079)
  - Box 25, folder 984 (Box 29, Folder 1080)
  - Box 25, folder 988 (Box 29, Folder 1081)
  - Box 25, folder 990 (Box 29, Folder 1082)
  - Box 25, folder 991 (Box 29, Folder 1083)
  - Box 26, folder 993 (Box 29, Folder 1084)
  - Box 26, folder 994 (Box 29, Folder 1085)
  - Box 26, folder 995 (Box 29, Folder 1086)
  - Box 26, folder 996 (Box 29, Folder 1087)
  - Box 26, folder 998 (Box 29, Folder 1088)
- Restricted Fragile Oversize, 2; (1 box)
  Restricted fragile material. For further information consult the appropriate curator.
  - Box 7, folder 361 (Box 30, Folder 1089)
  - Box 10, folder 458 (Box 30, Folder 1090)
  - Box 16, folder 759 (Box 30, Folder 1091)
  - Box 19, folder 871 (Box 30, Folder 1092)
  - Box 19, folder 880 (Box 30, Folder 1093)
  - Box 19, folder 883 (Box 30, Folder 1094)
  - Box 19, folder 887 (Box 30, Folder 1095)
  - Box 19, folder 889 (Box 30, Folder 1096)
  - Box 20, folder 894 (Box 30, Folder 1097)
  - Box 20, folder 895 (Box 30, Folder 1098)
  - Box 20, folder 896 (Box 30, Folder 1099)
  - Box 20, folder 898 (Box 30, Folder 1100)
  - Box 20, folder 900 (Box 30, Folder 1101)
  - Box 20, folder 904 (Box 30, Folder 1102)
  - Box 21, folder 907 (Box 30, Folder 1103)
  - Box 21, folder 911 (Box 30, Folder 1104)
  - Box 22, folder 922 (Box 30, Folder 1105)
  - Box 22, folder 924 (Box 30, Folder 1106)
  - Box 22, folder 925 (Box 30, Folder 1107)
  - Box 22, folder 934 (Box 30, Folder 1108)
  - Box 23, folder 937 (Box 30, Folder 1109)
  - Box 23, folder 958 (Box 30, Folder 1110)
  - Box 23, folder 959 (Box 30, Folder 1111)
  - Box 24, folder 967 (Box 30, Folder 1112)
  - Box 25, folder 978 (Box 30, Folder 1113)
  - Box 25, folder 979 (Box 30, Folder 1114)
  - Box 25, folder 981 (Box 30, Folder 1115)
  - Box 25, folder 983 (Box 30, Folder 1116)
  - Box 25, folder 985 (Box 30, Folder 1117)
  - Box 25, folder 986 (Box 30, Folder 1118)
  - Box 25, folder 987 (Box 30, Folder 1119)
  - Box 25, folder 988 (Box 30, Folder 1120)
  - Box 26, folder 993 (Box 30, Folder 1121)
  - Box 26, folder 994 (Box 30, Folder 1122)
  - Box 26, folder 995 (Box 30, Folder 1123)
  - Box 26, folder 996 (Box 30, Folder 1124)